DIMITRIU DRAGOS-ALEXANDRU



Contact details

Email: rapturereaper@gmail.com Skype- squallalex Phone +40743780249

About me

I'm a 33yo man, with over 7 years of accumulated healthcare experience in Romania as an orderly, and over 3 years in the UK as a care assistant. I decided to leave the UK due to ongoing political instabilities arising due to Brexit, and pursue my passions and hobbies related to animation, 3d modelling and others.

I've been an online freelancer, creating characters, 3d models and animations on various platforms since 2018.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Healthcare: 7 years (Ro)

Jun 2008 - Jul 2015 *Orderly - S.J.U Bacau (A&E)* 2015-2018-UK Care assistant at Chilmington House,

Duties as an orderly:

- -Sanitize my working environment as needed and instructed.(stretchers, beds, etc...)
- -Making and organizing residents' beds/rooms -Transport patients to and from different
- wards.
- -Liaise with doctors and nurses about patients' files and undergone procedures.
- -Maintain a professional attitude towards other members of staff.
- -Following doctors' and nurses' orders.
- -Preparing patients for surgeries, (shaving, personal hygiene.)
- -Helping other members of staff with collecting blood, urine samples.

Education

2000 - 2005

High School - Grigore Antipa

Subject-Ecology and environment protection Bacau

Foreign languages- English written/spoken - Advanced

Other info and qualifications

Orderly course (Ro) 2014

Other healthcare related courses (UK)